Please enable Javascript for easyhits4u.com domain in your browser.

Privacy Policy
==============

1. **Overview**  
    Thank you for visiting EasyHits4U.com (the "Web Site") and reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your privacy is important to us, and our policy is simple: we will collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Web Site unless you choose to provide that information. This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other sites, including those linked to or from the Web Site.  

2. **What Type of Information We Collect**  
    Personal Information together with other information is hereinafter referred to as “User Information”. We may collect or obtain User Information about you: directly from you (for example, upon registration or through the contact form); in the course of our relationship with you (e.g., if you make a purchase); when you make your Personal Information public (e.g., if you make your personal details public from the "Profile" section); when you install or use any of our Services; when you interact with any third party content on the Web Site. We may also receive User Information about you from third parties (e.g., Facebook or Google Sign-Up, or payment processor). We may also create User Information about you, such as records of your interactions with us. We are not responsible for Personal Information you spread about yourself in public areas of the Web Site.  

3. **Children's Issues**  
    The Web Site is not directed to children under thirteen (13) years of age; Sixteen (16) years or younger in the European Union. Children under such age must not use the web site or services offered on it to submit any individually identifiable information about themselves.  

4. **Copyright**  
    The materials found on the Web Site are protected by United States and other copyright laws, except for works of the United States Government pursuant to 1 U.S.C. Section 105. The selection, arrangement and presentation of all materials (including information in the public domain), and the overall design of the Web Site are copyright May 22, 2005, EasyHits4U.com. Any copying, distribution, retransmission or modification of information or materials on this site, whether in electronic or hard copy form, without the express prior written permission of EasyHits4U.com, is strictly prohibited.  

5. **No Warranties**  
    EasyHits4U.com does not make any express or implied warranties, representations or endorsements whatsoever (including, without limitation, the implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose) with regard to the Web Site, the materials, any products, information or service provided through the Web Site,, or any sites listed therein, and the Web Site will not be liable for any cost or damage arising either directly or indirectly from any such transaction. the Web Site does not warrant that it will be uninterrupted or error-free or that defects in it will be corrected. the web site is provided on an "as is, as available" basis.  
      
    In no event will the Web Site or its members, managers, officers, employees, agents and the assigns of same be liable for (1) any incidental, consequential or indirect damages (including, but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, business interruption, loss of programs or information, and the like) arising out of the use of or inability to use the web site, the materials or any information, or transactions provided on the web site or downloaded from the Web Site, even if the Web Site or its authorized representatives have been advised of the possibility of such damages, or (2) any claim attributable to errors, omissions or other inaccuracies in the web site, the materials and/or listings or information downloaded through the Web Site. Because some states do not allow the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, the above limitation may not apply to you. In such states, the Web Site's liability is limited to the greatest extent permitted by law.  

6. **Indemnification**  
    You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless the Web Site and its members, managers, officers, employees, agents and the assigns of same, from and against any and all loss, costs, expenses (including reasonable attorneys' fees and expenses), claims, damages and liabilities related to or associated with your use of the Web Site and any violation of this Privacy Policy by you.  

7. **Governing Law and Jurisdiction**  
    This Privacy Policy constitutes a contract made under and shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Ohio.  

8. **External Services Authorization**  
    Our Web Site uses OAuth for user authentication and for importing contacts on your request. We never request or have access to your Google, Facebook, Twitter, Yahoo, Microsoft, Apple, or Android passwords.  
      
    Through the acts of signing up, cancelling services, or disabling any of the features within our Web Site, users can control their data thereby limiting the use and disclosure of the basic personal information we collect. Additionally, users can revoke OAuth in Facebook, Google, Yahoo and Twitter which will remove EasyHits4U access to those systems.  
      
    During signup on the Web Site, personal information such as your name, email address, age and language can be requested. For the exact list of permissions and personal data please refer to particular page where data is being requested. It is your decision as to whether or not you provide this information.  

9. **Purposes for Which We May Process Your Information**  
    We may Process User Information for the following purposes: providing the Services to you; communicating with you; providing advertising to you on the Web Site; observing user engagement and purchase activity across the Web Site; marketing our services and offers to our customers; financial and IT management including the ensuring the security of our systems; conducting ; conducting polls, surveys or investigations where necessary; compliance with applicable law; and improving the Web Site Services.  
      
    EasyHits4U.com does not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes. We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to affiliates that provide services to us with regards to our Web Site (i.e. payment processors, Website hosting companies, etc.); such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective services. This Policy does not cover the practices of third parties who may provide information about you to the Web Site.  
      
    This website uses Pollfish web plugin. Pollfish is an on-line survey platform, through which, anyone may conduct surveys. Pollfish collaborates with Developers of applications for smartphones and website owners in order to have access to users of such applications/websites and address survey questionnaires to them. This website uses and enables Pollfish cookies. When a user connects to this website, Pollfish detects whether the user is eligible for a survey. Data collected by Pollfish will be associated with your answers to the questionnaires whenever Pollfish sents such questionnaires to eligible users. For a full list of data received by Pollfish through this website, please read carefully Pollfish respondent terms located at [https://www.pollfish.com/terms/respondent](https://www.pollfish.com/terms/respondent). By using this website you accept this privacy policy document and you hereby give your explicit consent for the placement of a Pollfish cookie in your system and the processing by Pollfish of the aforementioned data. Furthermore, you are informed that you may disable Pollfish operation at any time by using the Pollfish “opt out section” available on Pollfish website or by disabling “third party cookies” from your browser’s settings. We once more invite you to check the Pollfish respondent’s terms of use, if you wish to have more detailed view of the way Pollfish works.  
      
    APPLE, GOOGLE AND AMAZON ARE NOT A SPONSOR NOR ARE INVOLVED IN ANY WAY IN THIS CONTEST/DRAW. NO APPLE PRODUCTS ARE BEING USED AS PRIZES.  

10. **Data Deletion**  
    You have the right to request that we delete the Personal Information that we have collected from you. Once we receive a request, we will delete your personal information we have about you as of the date of your request from our database. This right is subject to certain exceptions. If your deletion request is subject to one of these exceptions, we may deny your deletion request.  

11. **Contact Information**  
    Queries or comments regarding the Web Site should be sent by [e-mail](mailto:info@easyhits4u.com), using [contact form](https://www.easyhits4u.com/contact.html) or by U.S. mail to M.P.O. Box 296, Oberlin, OH 44074-0296.  

12. **Last Update**  
    This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 17, 2023.
